So hello friends, welcome all of you again to
a new video.  Friends, if
your
mobile number is not linked to your bank account and you
want to create a new account in PhonePe, then friends, how
can you create a new account in PhonePe, we are going to tell you the same in today's video.
Friends, it does not matter whether
any mobile number is linked to your bank account
or not.
Friends, what is here is that you
can create a new account inside your PhonePe.  It does not matter whether
any mobile number is linked to your account or
not.  So
friends, in
today's video we are going to tell you how to create a new account in PhonePe.
So friends, what do you have to do
first to create a new account in PhonePe
?  You have to watch this video till the end.  That's why
friends, here
you can create a new account inside PhonePe.
Let's start the video without wasting any time.
Friends, we have come to our mobile
screens.  What do you have to do first after coming to the mobile screen
?
What do you have to do?  You have to open Play Store in your mobile phone.
So as soon as
you open Play Store in your mobile phone
, after opening Play Store,
you have to click on the search option here below.
So after clicking on the search option,
you have to search
PhonePe here.  So let me search PhonePe here.
So friends, as soon as
you search PhonePe here,
PhonePe will appear here.  So friends, what do you have to do here
?  PhonePe has to be installed and downloaded on your mobile phone.
So friends, here I have already
downloaded PhonePe in my mobile phone.
So you have to download it here.
After downloading etc.
what do you do from here?  It is simple,
you have to come back from here.  Let us come back.
So what do you have to do here after coming back
?  You have to open the PhonePe application on your mobile phone.
So
as soon as you open PhonePe on your mobile phone
, after opening PhonePe, an
interface like this will
open here.  What do you have to do when you
open the PhonePe application for the first time
?
You have to login here by entering your mobile number etc.
So here I am already logged in.
What do you have to do here after logging in etc.?
You have to click on the option of your logo on the left side.
Let us click on this.
Now friends, as soon as you
click on this, you can see that
I have placed a photo here.  So the
photo is showing here.  After that friends,
what do you have to do here?  Here you will
see an option of Manage Payments.  So
what do you have to do here?  You just have to simply
click on the Manage Payments option.  Let
us click on this.  Now friends,
as soon as you
click on the Manage Payments option here, after that an
interface like this will open here.
Here you
will see an option for UPI bank accounts.  So
friends, what do you have to do here?
You have to click on this here once.
Let's click on this.  So,
after clicking on this, friends, here you
can see that my two bank
accounts are already linked here.  So here I will
unlink both the bank accounts right now.
So what simple thing can we do to unlink
?  Click on your bank account.
After clicking on Bank Account,
we will scroll down here.
After scrolling down, here we will
click on Unlink Bank Account.
After that, here again we will
click on the unlink option.  So let's click on unlink.
After that, you can see here
that the bank account has been successfully
unlinked.  Again, here
we unlink the other bank account from here.
What will we do here for this?  Click on bank account.
After clicking on bank account,
scroll down.  And after that,
here we will click on Unlink Bank Account again
and from here we will
click on Unlink.  As soon as we
click on this, you can see here
that both the bank accounts have been successfully
unlinked.  After that
friends, what do you have to do here?
Friends, what do you have to do here?  Here
you have to again click on the option of Add New Bank Account.
So let us
click on this.  Friends, as soon as
you click on Add Bank Account here, an
interface like this will open here.  Now friends,
what do you have to do here?  Here you have to
select your bank account.
Friends, if your bank account
is not showing here then you
can click on the search option above.  So as soon as
you click on the search option here,
you have to enter the name of your bank account here.
Your
bank account will appear here.  So
my account here is in Punjab National Bank.
Friends, Punjab National Bank is
not linked to our mobile number.
So now we are going to
create our account on PhonePe through this bank account.
So what will we do here?  You will select your bank
account.  You have to
select whichever bank account you want.
So what will we do here?
Click on Punjab National Bank once.
Clicked it.  So friends, as soon as
we clicked on our bank account,
after clicking on the bank account, friends, here
you can see that it is written No
Account Found.  So friends, you don't have to
worry here.  Just keep
watching the video till the end.  So friends,
what do you have to do here?  Here you have to
click on the cut option.  After clicking on this,
friends, from here you have to simply go back to
PhonePe.
Friends, after coming back, what do you have to do here
?  You have to refresh everything from here.  Let's
refresh ourselves.  So here
I refreshed everyone.  After refreshing,
you have to open the PhonePe application again in your mobile phone.
Now after opening it, an
interface like this will open here.
After opening, here
you have to click again on the left side at the top.
Let us click on this.
Now as soon as you
click on it here.  After that, here you have to
click again on the Manage Payments option.
Let us click on this.  So
as soon as you
click on the Manage Payments option here.  Friends,
what do you have to do here?  Have to scroll down.
Let us scroll down.
So friends, as soon as you scroll down here
,
after scrolling down you will see an option of
UPI settings here.  So friends,
what do you have to do here?  You have to
click on the UPI settings option.  Let's
click on this.  Now friends, as soon as
you click on this, an
interface like this will open here.
Add bank account.  So friends, let
me tell you here.  Here, whatever
bank account you add,
you can only receive money in this bank account.
From here you cannot send money to anyone etc.
because friends,
your mobile number is not linked to your bank account.
So friends, what do
you have to do here to add your bank account
?  Click on the option of add bank account.
Let us click on this.
Now friends, as soon as
you click on Add Bank Account here,
after that some such
interface will open here.  Friends,
what do you have to do here?  You have to select your bank
account.  Here you can enter the
bank account which you
want to link.  So here we are going to
link the Punjab National Bank account now.
So what will we do here?  You will
select your bank account.
After selecting the bank account, you have to allow
all the permissions asked here.  Okay,
we allowed it.
After allowing, your
mobile number will be verified here.
Here you have to wait for a few seconds.
Let us wait.  So
after waiting, you can see here that the
verification has been successfully
completed.  After that,
fetching your account details will appear here.  Here
you have to wait again for a few seconds.
So friends, after waiting,
you can see here that the bank account has been
successfully added here in
PhonePe.  Now friends, what do you have to do here
?  Here below you have to
click on the Done option.  Now friends,
what do you have to do here to receive the money?  You have to come back from here.
So friends, after coming back, here
you have to click on the option of QR Code S UPI ID.
Let us click on this.
So friends,
you can receive the money on this QR code.
Maybe friends, you
can also send money through PhonePe.  Friends, if you
send money through PhonePe then comment below the video.
So friends, in this way
you can also create a new account in PhonePe without linking any mobile number to your bank account.
So I hope
you like this video.  If you like the video, please
like the video.  Subscribe to the channel.
See you
in the next video.